<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>anime RSS - OtakuKart</title>
    <link>https://otakukart.com</link>
    <description>OtakuKart RSS 피드</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 15:47:18 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>David Dastmalchian Talks About The Pressure Of Bringing One Piece Villain Mr. 3 To Live Action</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/david-dastmalchian-talks-about-the-pressure-of-bringing-one-piece-villain-mr-3-to-live-action/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/david-dastmalchian-talks-about-the-pressure-of-bringing-one-piece-villain-mr-3-to-live-action/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:31:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>Stepping into a long-established manga role comes with unavoidable pressure, and David Dastmalchian felt that weight while preparing to play Mr. 3 in One Piece Live Action Season 2 Mr. 3, also known as Galdino, is a major antagonist introduced during the Little Garden arc, known for his calculating personality and Wax-Wax abilities. The character [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Piece Actor David Dastmalchian Explains Why Iñaki Godoy Is The Perfect Real-Life Luffy</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/one-piece-actor-david-dastmalchian-explains-why-inaki-godoy-is-the-perfect-real-life-luffy/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/one-piece-actor-david-dastmalchian-explains-why-inaki-godoy-is-the-perfect-real-life-luffy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 12:14:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>Casting Monkey D. Luffy was always going to be the most closely watched decision behind One Piece. But according to David Dastmalchian, the production didn’t just cast Luffy; they found him. Speaking about his time on set, Dastmalchian shared why he believes Iñaki Godoy naturally embodies the spirit of Eiichiro Oda’s iconic protagonist. When asked [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romelia War Chronicle Confirms Cast and AnimeJapan 2026 Appearance</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/romelia-war-chronicle-confirms-cast-and-animejapan-2026-appearance/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/romelia-war-chronicle-confirms-cast-and-animejapan-2026-appearance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:46:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>Romelia War Chronicle moves forward with its 2026 anime adaptation, revealing its teaser visual, main cast, and upcoming stage event at AnimeJapan 2026. Carrying the tagline “I shall start again from here,” the series presents a post–Demon King narrative centered on resurgence and reconstruction, led by one determined young woman and the knights who stand [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atarayo Returns With Reflective Pop Ballad ‘Spring Is Coming’</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/atarayo-returns-with-reflective-pop-ballad-spring-is-coming/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/atarayo-returns-with-reflective-pop-ballad-spring-is-coming/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:37:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>As the seasons begin to shift, Atarayo returns with a new emotionally resonant single, “Spring Is Coming (春となり).” The track appears as an insert song in the nationwide theatrical release of The Dangers in My Heart (僕の心のヤバイやつ). Structured as a sweeping mid-tempo ballad grounded in detailed lyrical storytelling, the song carries layered meaning. When Winter [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Sejeong at a Crossroads: Contract Renewal Discussions with Jellyfish Entertainment and Future Career Prospects</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/kim-sejeong-at-a-crossroads-contract-renewal-discussions-with-jellyfish-entertainment-and-future-career-prospects/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/kim-sejeong-at-a-crossroads-contract-renewal-discussions-with-jellyfish-entertainment-and-future-career-prospects/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:29:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>On February 20, 2026, reports surfaced regarding the future of Kim Sejeong’s career as her long-standing contract with Jellyfish Entertainment approaches its expiration. After an impactful decade-long journey with the agency, the multi-talented star is reportedly considering a variety of paths for her next chapter. This news has sparked significant interest among fans and industry [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTS’s V Faces Public Scrutiny and Netizen Backlash Following Statement on Private Messages Used in Court</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/btss-v-faces-public-scrutiny-and-netizen-backlash-following-statement-on-private-messages-used-in-court/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/btss-v-faces-public-scrutiny-and-netizen-backlash-following-statement-on-private-messages-used-in-court/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:22:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>The ongoing legal warfare between HYBE and former ADOR CEO Min Hee Jin has pulled a high-profile figure into its epicenter, resulting in a complicated public relations situation for BTS member V (Kim Taehyung). On February 20, 2026, V found himself at the center of a heated online debate after he posted an Instagram story [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOYNEXTDOOR’s Sungho to Release First Solo OST for the Korean Launch of ‘5 Centimeters per Second’</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/boynextdoors-sungho-to-release-first-solo-ost-for-the-korean-launch-of-5-centimeters-per-second/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/boynextdoors-sungho-to-release-first-solo-ost-for-the-korean-launch-of-5-centimeters-per-second/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:19:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>The K-pop industry is buzzing with excitement as Sungho, a prominent member of the rising boy group BOYNEXTDOOR, prepares to reach a significant milestone in his career. On February 20, 2026, it was officially announced that Sungho will be lending his emotive vocals to the official soundtrack (OST) of the Korean release of the live-action [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTS’s J-Hope Faces Uncomfortable Interactions During Livestream and Global Tour</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/btss-j-hope-faces-uncomfortable-interactions-during-livestream-and-global-tour/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/btss-j-hope-faces-uncomfortable-interactions-during-livestream-and-global-tour/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:13:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>The K-pop world has been buzzing with a mix of celebration and concern following recent events involving BTS’s J-Hope. While the multi-talented artist celebrated his 31st birthday on February 18, 2026, with a record-breaking livestream, the occasion was slightly marred by inappropriate fan behavior and a controversial complaint during his broadcast. These incidents have once [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTS’s V Breaks Silence on Private Messages with Min Hee Jin Being Used as Court Evidence</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/btss-v-breaks-silence-on-private-messages-with-min-hee-jin-being-used-as-court-evidence/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/btss-v-breaks-silence-on-private-messages-with-min-hee-jin-being-used-as-court-evidence/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:06:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>The complex legal battle between HYBE and the former CEO of ADOR, Min Hee Jin, has taken an unexpected turn involving one of the world’s most prominent idols. On February 20, 2026, BTS member V (Kim Taehyung) personally addressed the controversy surrounding his private KakaoTalk messages, which were recently revealed to have been submitted as [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTS’s RM to Curate Prestigious Art Exhibition at SFMOMA: A Fusion of Music, Identity, and Fine Art</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/btss-rm-to-curate-prestigious-art-exhibition-at-sfmoma-a-fusion-of-music-identity-and-fine-art/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/btss-rm-to-curate-prestigious-art-exhibition-at-sfmoma-a-fusion-of-music-identity-and-fine-art/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>BTS leader RM (Kim Namjoon), widely recognized as a sophisticated art collector and advocate, will officially curate a major exhibition at the San Francisco Museum of Modern Art (SFMOMA). Announced on February 19, 2026, this landmark event marks one of the first times a global K-pop icon has taken on such a central curatorial role [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MediaOCD Announces Expanded Slate of Discotek Collector Editions</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/mediaocd-announces-expanded-slate-of-discotek-collector-editions/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/mediaocd-announces-expanded-slate-of-discotek-collector-editions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:49:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>MediaOCD has announced a major expansion of its DISCOTEK DEEP DIVE initiative, revealing more than 20 additional classic anime titles from Discotek Media that are now available for pre-order exclusively through the MediaOCD website. The DISCOTEK DEEP DIVE program was created to spotlight hard-to-find and out-of-print releases from Discotek Media’s extensive catalog. Each month, MediaOCD [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix Sets March Premiere for Steel Ball Run JoJo’s Bizarre Adventure</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/netflix-sets-march-premiere-for-steel-ball-run-jojos-bizarre-adventure/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/netflix-sets-march-premiere-for-steel-ball-run-jojos-bizarre-adventure/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:43:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>“Whoever does win this race will be a hero to the whole world.” The next chapter in the globally celebrated JoJo&amp;#8217;s Bizarre Adventure saga is set to arrive. Fans can now watch the newly released English-dubbed trailer for STEEL BALL RUN JoJo’s Bizarre Adventure and meet the English voice cast bringing the epic cross-continental race [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kagurabachi Chapter 113: Spoilers, Predictions &amp; Recap</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/kagurabachi-chapter-113-spoilers-predictions-recap/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/kagurabachi-chapter-113-spoilers-predictions-recap/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:52:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>Kagurabachi Chapter 113 is set to release very soon. Chapter 112 serves as a powerful and emotionally loaded end to Part One of Kagurabachi, and it sticks the landing in almost every way that matters. Titled &amp;#8220;Future,&amp;#8221; the chapter does exactly what a finale should it closes one door while leaving another wide open, giving [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Was Freaks and Geeks Cancelled? NBC’s Ratings Roulette Killed a Future Hit</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/why-was-freaks-and-geeks-cancelled-nbcs-ratings-roulette-killed-a-future-hit/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/why-was-freaks-and-geeks-cancelled-nbcs-ratings-roulette-killed-a-future-hit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:13:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>NBC dumped Freaks and Geeks into the Saturday 8 PM slot back in 1999, a graveyard for fresh shows chasing teen eyes. Kids ditched TVs for hangouts, leaving Lindsay Weir&amp;#8217;s crew to scrap against cartoons and game shows with zero shot at steady buzz. Episodes dropped out of order, stretched by weeks-long hiatuses for baseball [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLOSE YOUR EYES Member Jang Yeojun Announces Temporary Hiatus Due to Medical Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/close-your-eyes-member-jang-yeojun-announces-temporary-hiatus-due-to-medical-diagnosis/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/close-your-eyes-member-jang-yeojun-announces-temporary-hiatus-due-to-medical-diagnosis/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:35:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>In an unexpected development for fans of the rising K-pop group CLOSE YOUR EYES, the group’s agency, UNCORE, has announced that member Jang Yeojun will be taking an immediate leave of absence from all group activities. The news broke on February 19, 2026, via an official statement released on the group&amp;#8217;s social media channels and [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE BOYZ’s Eric Officially Debuts Personal Account on X</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/the-boyzs-eric-officially-debuts-personal-account-on-x/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/the-boyzs-eric-officially-debuts-personal-account-on-x/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:32:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>In an exciting move for &amp;#8220;TheB&amp;#8221; (the official fandom of THE BOYZ), member Eric has officially expanded his digital presence by launching a personal account on X, the platform formerly known as Twitter. On February 18, 2026, the idol surprised fans by opening the account, marking a new chapter in how he communicates with his [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;TEAM Officially Reveals Dates and Cities for 2026 Asia Tour BLAZE THE WAY</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/team-officially-reveals-dates-and-cities-for-2026-asia-tour-blaze-the-way/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/team-officially-reveals-dates-and-cities-for-2026-asia-tour-blaze-the-way/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:27:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>On February 19, 2026, the globally rising boy group &amp;#38;TEAM thrilled their international fanbase by announcing the official itinerary for their highly anticipated 2026 concert tour. Titled &amp;#8220;BLAZE THE WAY,&amp;#8221; the tour represents a significant milestone for the group as they continue to expand their footprint across Asia and beyond. This latest announcement provides a [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTS’s j-hope Celebrates 2026 Birthday with Major Philanthropic Contributions</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/btss-j-hope-celebrates-2026-birthday-with-major-philanthropic-contributions/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/btss-j-hope-celebrates-2026-birthday-with-major-philanthropic-contributions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:24:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>BTS member j-hope has once again demonstrated why his stage name is synonymous with positivity and altruism. To mark his birthday on February 18, 2026, the superstar chose to celebrate by making a series of significant donations totaling hundreds of millions of won. These contributions, aimed at supporting vulnerable children, aspiring students, and animal welfare, [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actress Uhm Ji Won Undergoes Surgery Following Unfortunate Accident in Tokyo</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/actress-uhm-ji-won-undergoes-surgery-following-unfortunate-accident-in-tokyo/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/actress-uhm-ji-won-undergoes-surgery-following-unfortunate-accident-in-tokyo/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:20:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>Prominent South Korean actress Uhm Ji Won is currently on the mend after a sudden injury disrupted her professional schedule. On February 14, 2026, while visiting Tokyo, Japan, the actress suffered a fall that resulted in a fracture to her left ankle. The news was confirmed by her management agency, ABM Company, who shared that [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTS Jin’s Casual Mirror Selfie Triggers Global Sell-Out of Luxury Gucci Accessory</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/bts-jins-casual-mirror-selfie-triggers-global-sell-out-of-luxury-gucci-accessory/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/bts-jins-casual-mirror-selfie-triggers-global-sell-out-of-luxury-gucci-accessory/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:17:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>BTS member Jin has once again solidified his reputation as the ultimate &amp;#8220;Sold Out King,&amp;#8221; proving that even a simple &amp;#8220;off-work&amp;#8221; update can shift global markets in a matter of minutes. On February 14, 2026, the world-renowned superstar took to the fan community platform Weverse to share a glimpse of his daily life. What began [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creepy Nuts Confirm 2026 North American Dates, Including Coachella Performances</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/creepy-nuts-confirm-2026-north-american-dates-including-coachella-performances/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/creepy-nuts-confirm-2026-north-american-dates-including-coachella-performances/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>Japanese hip-hop force Creepy Nuts, composed of three-time national rap battle champion R-Shitei and world champion DJ DJ Matsunaga, have announced their first-ever North American tour. The Creepy Nuts North America Tour 2026 marks a pivotal step in the duo’s accelerating international trajectory. The tour itinerary includes their debut appearances at the Coachella Valley Music [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VERIVERY’s Kangmin Steps Into the Spotlight With His First Solo Debut</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/veriverys-kangmin-steps-into-the-spotlight-with-his-first-solo-debut/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/veriverys-kangmin-steps-into-the-spotlight-with-his-first-solo-debut/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:39:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>Kangmin of the K-pop boy group VERIVERY is officially preparing to embark on a new chapter in his career. Kangmin has been confirmed to make his long-awaited solo debut, marking a major milestone since his group debut in 2019. The news has quickly generated excitement among fans, who have watched him grow from the youngest [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Crayon Pop Member ChoA Hospitalized Ahead of Twin Birth</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/former-crayon-pop-member-choa-hospitalized-ahead-of-twin-birth/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/former-crayon-pop-member-choa-hospitalized-ahead-of-twin-birth/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:58:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>Choa, formerly of the popular K-pop girl group Crayon Pop, recently shared an update about her health as she approaches the final stage of her pregnancy. The singer revealed that she has been hospitalized for precautionary medical care ahead of the birth of her twins, prompting concern and support from fans. Choa explained that she [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Paradox of Exhaustion: Jennie’s No Sleep Reveal Triggers a Storm of Lazy Allegations</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/the-paradox-of-exhaustion-jennies-no-sleep-reveal-triggers-a-storm-of-lazy-allegations/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/the-paradox-of-exhaustion-jennies-no-sleep-reveal-triggers-a-storm-of-lazy-allegations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:51:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>The life of a global K-pop icon is often viewed through a lens of glamour, sold-out stadiums, and high-fashion campaigns. However, a recent viral firestorm surrounding BLACKPINK’s Jennie has pulled back the curtain on the industry’s grueling demands, while simultaneously exposing the relentless scrutiny the idol faces. A resurfaced comment from Jennie regarding her promotion [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTS Jimin Faces Unfounded Plastic Surgery Rumors That Spark Online Controversy</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/bts-jimin-faces-unfounded-plastic-surgery-rumors-that-spark-online-controversy/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/bts-jimin-faces-unfounded-plastic-surgery-rumors-that-spark-online-controversy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:41:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>Jimin of BTS recently became the center of online discussion after unverified plastic surgery rumors resurfaced across social media platforms. The controversy began when users compared photos of Jimin from different stages of his career and made speculative claims about changes in his facial features. Despite the lack of any official confirmation or credible evidence, [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jungkook’s Self-Produced Fan Song MY YOU Surpasses 170 Million Streams on Spotify</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/jungkooks-self-produced-fan-song-my-you-surpasses-170-million-streams-on-spotify/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/jungkooks-self-produced-fan-song-my-you-surpasses-170-million-streams-on-spotify/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:35:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>Jungkook’s self-produced song “MY YOU” has reached an impressive milestone on Spotify, surpassing 170 million streams. This achievement highlights the song’s widespread popularity around the world and shows how deeply fans continue to connect with his music- especially when it comes directly from his own creative expression. “MY YOU” started as a special track made [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Truth Behind the Racism Allegations Against BLACKPINK’s Jisoo</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/the-truth-behind-the-racism-allegations-against-blackpinks-jisoo/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/the-truth-behind-the-racism-allegations-against-blackpinks-jisoo/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:12:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>The K-pop world has recently been shaken by a wave of intense controversy as BLACKPINK’s Jisoo became the target of serious, yet highly contested, allegations of racism towards her fellow member, Lisa. The situation escalated rapidly on social media, sparking a fierce battle between those accusing the idol of insensitive behavior and millions of fans [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lim Young Woong Captures Triple Crown at the 33rd Hanteo Music Awards</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/lim-young-woong-captures-triple-crown-at-the-33rd-hanteo-music-awards/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/lim-young-woong-captures-triple-crown-at-the-33rd-hanteo-music-awards/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:06:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>Lim Young Woong achieved a major milestone at the 33rd Hanteo Music Awards, taking home three top honors and standing out as one of the biggest winners of the night. The Hanteo Music Awards are known for recognizing artists based on actual album sales recorded by the Hanteo Chart, which tracks real-time physical sales in [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Soo Hyun’s Fan Union Donates 100 Million KRW to Celebrate His Birthday</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/kim-soo-hyuns-fan-union-donates-100-million-krw-to-celebrate-his-birthday/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/kim-soo-hyuns-fan-union-donates-100-million-krw-to-celebrate-his-birthday/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>Kim Soo Hyun, one of South Korea’s most beloved actors, was recently honored in a meaningful way by his fans. In celebration of his birthday, a coordinated fan union made a donation of 100 million Korean won (KRW)- approximately 75,000 USD- to charitable causes. This effort reflects not only their admiration for him as an [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oda admits the next One Piece movie is not progressing smoothly and issues a public call out to staff</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/oda-admits-the-next-one-piece-movie-is-not-progressing-smoothly-and-issues-a-public-call-out-to-staff/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/oda-admits-the-next-one-piece-movie-is-not-progressing-smoothly-and-issues-a-public-call-out-to-staff/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 02:37:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>The Oda Letter at Jump Festa has long been the primary scripture for the One Piece community, but his message at Jump Festa 2026 took an uncharacteristically sharp turn. Moving beyond the usual teases of that island and those two people meeting, Eiichiro Oda issued a public ultimatum to Toei Animation that has effectively put [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Piece Chapter 1175: Spoilers, Pics &amp; Summary</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/one-piece-chapter-1175-spoilers-pics-summary/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/one-piece-chapter-1175-spoilers-pics-summary/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 22:38:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>This thread is exclusively for spoiler pics and summaries related to One Piece Chapter 1175. For discussions, please use the One Piece Chapter 1175 Discussion thread. Do not post spoilers in the discussion thread. THIS IS A LIVE UPDATING POST – SCROLL DOWN FOR SPOILERS Thread Availability &amp;#38; Posting Rules The One Piece Chapter 1175 [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happened to Robert Duvall? Hollywood Icon’s Enduring Legacy</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/what-happened-to-robert-duvall-hollywood-icons-enduring-legacy/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/what-happened-to-robert-duvall-hollywood-icons-enduring-legacy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:34:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>Robert Duvall established himself early with a chilling performance as Boo Radley in the 1962 classic To Kill a Mockingbird. That silent, eerie role introduced his intense screen presence to audiences alongside Gregory Peck. He transitioned through various television westerns and police dramas to refine his craft before achieving major cinematic breakthroughs. The 1970s marked [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLACKPINK Fans Torn Over Alleged Leaks and the Bebe Rexha Mystery</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/the-deadline-drama-blackpink-fans-torn-over-alleged-leaks-and-the-bebe-rexha-mystery/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/the-deadline-drama-blackpink-fans-torn-over-alleged-leaks-and-the-bebe-rexha-mystery/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:53:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>The K-pop world is currently in a state of high-octane anticipation and internal conflict as BLACKPINK prepares for the release of their third mini-album, &amp;#8220;DEADLINE,&amp;#8221; officially scheduled to drop on February 27, 2026. While the announcement of their first group project in over three years initially sent BLINKs into a frenzy of excitement, the mood [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Park Na-rae’s Disney+ Appearance Sparks Boycott Calls Amid Embezzlement Battle</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/fate-at-a-crossroads-park-na-raes-disney-appearance-sparks-boycott-calls-amid-embezzlement-battle/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/fate-at-a-crossroads-park-na-raes-disney-appearance-sparks-boycott-calls-amid-embezzlement-battle/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:46:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>The South Korean entertainment industry is currently witnessing a stark confrontation between corporate release schedules and public sentiment. Comedian Park Na-rae, a mainstay of Korean variety for over a decade, has found her &amp;#8220;comeback&amp;#8221; on the Disney+ original series Battle of Fates (also known as Fate War 49) overshadowed by a massive viewer boycott. According [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cha Eun-woo’s Tax Crisis Clouds Netflix’s The WONDERfools</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/scandal-and-superpowers-cha-eun-woos-tax-crisis-clouds-netflixs-the-wonderfools/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/scandal-and-superpowers-cha-eun-woos-tax-crisis-clouds-netflixs-the-wonderfools/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>The unblemished &amp;#8220;model student&amp;#8221; image of actor and ASTRO member Cha Eun-woo has been severely shaken as he faces the largest tax reassessment ever sought from an individual South Korean celebrity. According to recent reports from The Korea Herald and OSEN, the actor is currently embroiled in an investigation by the National Tax Service (NTS) [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KATSEYE’s Historic Grammy Night Ignites ‘Bought’ Controversy</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/breaking-the-glass-ceiling-katseyes-historic-grammy-night-ignites-bought-controversy/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/breaking-the-glass-ceiling-katseyes-historic-grammy-night-ignites-bought-controversy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:37:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>The 68th Annual Grammy Awards, held on February 1, 2026, became a monumental landmark for global music as KATSEYE, the joint-venture group between HYBE and Geffen Records, took the stage. Their presence marked a historic milestone: KATSEYE became the first girl group to perform and be nominated in the General Field (Best New Artist) in [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoA Parts Ways with SM Entertainment After 25 Years</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/the-end-of-an-era-boa-parts-ways-with-sm-entertainment-after-25-years-2/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/the-end-of-an-era-boa-parts-ways-with-sm-entertainment-after-25-years-2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:32:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>The landscape of K-pop has shifted fundamentally with the news that BoA, the legendary &amp;#8220;Star of Asia,&amp;#8221; has officially ended her 25-year partnership with SM Entertainment. On January 12, 2026, the agency confirmed that her exclusive contract concluded as of December 31, 2025. While the official statements from both parties were filled with mutual respect [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HoverLab and Gold Medalist Clash Over Kim Sae-ron’s 700 Million Won Debt</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/breaking-down-the-legal-war-hoverlab-and-gold-medalist-clash-over-kim-sae-rons-700-million-won-debt/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/breaking-down-the-legal-war-hoverlab-and-gold-medalist-clash-over-kim-sae-rons-700-million-won-debt/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:25:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>The tragic narrative surrounding the late Kim Sae-ron has entered a volatile new chapter on the first anniversary of her passing. As reported by Koreaboo and multiple Korean news outlets, a fierce &amp;#8220;legal war&amp;#8221; has erupted between the controversial YouTube channel HoverLab (Garo Sero Institute) and Gold Medalist, the agency representing Kim Soo-hyun. At the [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Sae-ron’s Death Anniversary and the Kim Soo-hyun Legal War</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/a-year-of-unresolved-sorrow-kim-sae-rons-death-anniversary-and-the-kim-soo-hyun-legal-war/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/a-year-of-unresolved-sorrow-kim-sae-rons-death-anniversary-and-the-kim-soo-hyun-legal-war/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:18:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>February 16, 2026, marks the somber first anniversary of the passing of former child star Kim Sae-ron. While the day should have been a time for quiet remembrance of the actress- who rose to fame in The Man from Nowhere- it has instead become a lightning rod for an escalating legal battle. The controversy involves [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedian Jo Se-ho’s Career Spirals Amid Organized Crime and Gambling Allegations</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/shadow-of-the-underworld-comedian-jo-se-hos-career-spirals-amid-organized-crime-and-gambling-allegations/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/shadow-of-the-underworld-comedian-jo-se-hos-career-spirals-amid-organized-crime-and-gambling-allegations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 08:30:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>The South Korean entertainment industry is currently reeling from one of its most shocking scandals of 2026, as beloved comedian and broadcaster Jo Se-ho remains in a state of professional &amp;#8220;limbo.&amp;#8221; Once a mainstay on national variety shows alongside icons like Yoo Jae-seok, Jo’s career has been derailed by explosive allegations linking him to organized [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Era of Early Manga Leaks is Finally Facing a Terminal Threat as Japan Launches a Trillion-Yen Offensive</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/the-era-of-early-manga-leaks-is-finally-facing-a-terminal-threat-as-japan-launches-a-trillion-yen-offensive/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/the-era-of-early-manga-leaks-is-finally-facing-a-terminal-threat-as-japan-launches-a-trillion-yen-offensive/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:27:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>The Hayabare, better known as early leak culture outside of Japan, has defined the manga community for decades and is now facing a terminal threat. Japan’s four publishing titans Shueisha, Kodansha, Shogakukan, and Kadokawa have moved beyond simple warnings into a state of total war. This coordinated offensive targets the entire piracy supply chain, from [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The “MZ Wannabe Icons” Return: IVE Announces June 2026 Australia and New Zealand Leg</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/the-mz-wannabe-icons-return-ive-announces-june-2026-australia-and-new-zealand-leg/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/the-mz-wannabe-icons-return-ive-announces-june-2026-australia-and-new-zealand-leg/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 10:11:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>The global K-pop phenomenon IVE has officially confirmed that their second world tour, IVE WORLD TOUR , will touch down in Australia and New Zealand in June 2026. This announcement, made on February 16, 2026, marks the group&amp;#8217;s highly anticipated return to the region following their successful 2024 debut. While the six-member group—ANYUJIN, GAEUL, REI, [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient Echoes, Modern Icons: The National Museum of Korea X Blackpink Merchandise Reveal</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/ancient-echoes-modern-icons-the-national-museum-of-korea-x-blackpink-merchandise-reveal/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/ancient-echoes-modern-icons-the-national-museum-of-korea-x-blackpink-merchandise-reveal/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 10:07:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>The intersection of millennial pop culture and millennial-old history has officially reached its commercial peak. Following the announcement of their landmark collaboration, the National Museum of Korea (NMK) and YG Entertainment have revealed the official &amp;#8220;Heritage Collection&amp;#8221; for Blackpink’s third EP, Deadline. This exclusive merchandise line is designed to reflect the group’s &amp;#8220;radiant present&amp;#8221; while [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising Star Lee Chae Min Eyes Lead Role in Webtoon-Based Romance Drama “My Reason to Die”</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/rising-star-lee-chae-min-eyes-lead-role-in-webtoon-based-romance-drama-my-reason-to-die-2/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/rising-star-lee-chae-min-eyes-lead-role-in-webtoon-based-romance-drama-my-reason-to-die-2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:54:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>The South Korean entertainment industry is buzzing with the news of the new project of Lee Chae Min. On February 12, 2026, it was reported that the rising actor is in talks to star in an upcoming drama titled “My Reason to Die” (working title). His agency, VARO Entertainment, confirmed the news shortly after, stating [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Reunion: Seoul Braces for Historic Crowds as BTS Claims Gwanghwamun</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/the-great-reunion-seoul-braces-for-historic-crowds-as-bts-claims-gwanghwamun/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/the-great-reunion-seoul-braces-for-historic-crowds-as-bts-claims-gwanghwamun/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:47:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>The heart of Seoul is preparing for a logistical feat of historic proportions. On March 21, 2026, BTS will hold their first full-group live performance in nearly four years at Gwanghwamun Square. Titled &amp;#8220;BTS The Comeback Live: Arirang,&amp;#8221; the free concert is the centerpiece of a citywide celebration following the March 20 release of their [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Return of the Kings: BTS “Arirang” World Tour Sets a New Global Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/the-return-of-the-kings-bts-arirang-world-tour-sets-a-new-global-benchmark/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/the-return-of-the-kings-bts-arirang-world-tour-sets-a-new-global-benchmark/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:42:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>The global music industry is currently bracing for an unprecedented economic and cultural event as BigHit Music officially confirms the BTS World Tour &amp;#8220;Arirang.&amp;#8221; Marking the group’s first full-scale reunion tour since the completion of their mandatory military service, the tour is designed to be the largest in K-pop history. Spanning 82 shows across 34 [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Commercial Chill: Retailers Sound the Alarm as MADEIN Pre-Orders Stall</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/the-commercial-chill-retailers-sound-the-alarm-as-madein-pre-orders-stall/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/the-commercial-chill-retailers-sound-the-alarm-as-madein-pre-orders-stall/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:38:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>As of February 2026, the retail landscape for K-pop has shifted from anticipation to apprehension. Major domestic and international music retailers are reporting a significant downturn in pre-order volumes for MADEIN’s upcoming album, a direct consequence of the ongoing criminal investigation into 143 Entertainment’s CEO. While the group’s debut was once expected to be a [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Margin Squeeze: Why Analysts Are Cooling on HYBE’s Record-Breaking 2025?</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/the-margin-squeeze-why-analysts-are-cooling-on-hybes-record-breaking-2025/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/the-margin-squeeze-why-analysts-are-cooling-on-hybes-record-breaking-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:34:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>While HYBE Co. Ltd. (KRX:352820) successfully navigated a year of massive global expansion and record-shattering revenue, the financial community has reacted to the company’s recent Q4 earnings report with a mix of caution and strategic skepticism. Despite generating an all-time high of $1.86 billion (2.65 trillion KRW) in revenue for the full year, the company’s [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital Dynasties: Netflix and BTS Redefine Global Live Streaming</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/digital-dynasties-netflix-and-bts-redefine-global-live-streaming/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/digital-dynasties-netflix-and-bts-redefine-global-live-streaming/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:29:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>The global entertainment landscape is on the verge of a historic shift as Netflix officially secures the exclusive global livestream rights for the BTS Gwanghwamun Square comeback concert. This partnership, announced in early February 2026, marks the streaming giant’s most significant foray into live K-pop content, broadcasting the event to over 190 countries and approximately [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safeguarding Artists: BELIFT LAB Issues Comprehensive New Fan Etiquette Guidelines for ENHYPEN</title>
      <link>https://otakukart.com/safeguarding-artists-belift-lab-issues-comprehensive-new-fan-etiquette-guidelines-for-enhypen/</link>
      <guid>https://otakukart.com/safeguarding-artists-belift-lab-issues-comprehensive-new-fan-etiquette-guidelines-for-enhypen/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 16:21:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>On February 13, 2026, BELIFT LAB, the agency representing the global K-pop sensation ENHYPEN, released an extensive and updated set of fan etiquette guidelines. This initiative aims to foster a healthier fan culture while providing robust protection for the rights, safety, and privacy of the group members. The agency expressed deep gratitude to the fandom, [&amp;#8230;]</content:encoded>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>