<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>anime RSS - Anime Daily</title>
    <link>https://www.theanimedaily.com</link>
    <description>Anime Daily RSS 피드</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 16:14:37 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Apothecary Diaries Season 3 Gets Greenlight With Original Anime Movie</title>
      <link>https://www.theanimedaily.com/the-apothecary-diaries-season-3-release-date-movie/</link>
      <guid>https://www.theanimedaily.com/the-apothecary-diaries-season-3-release-date-movie/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:45:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>
        &lt;p&gt;The Apothecary Diaries&amp;#160;has quietly become one of the most critically admired anime series of recent years. What started as a slow-burning historical mystery evolved into a character-driven drama that balances intellect, politics, and emotional depth. Now, with&amp;#160;The Apothecary Diaries Season 3 officially renewed, fans finally have clarity on what comes next—and when. Season 3 will [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theanimedaily.com/the-apothecary-diaries-season-3-release-date-movie/&quot;&gt;The Apothecary Diaries Season 3 Gets Greenlight With Original Anime Movie&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theanimedaily.com&quot;&gt;The Anime Daily&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr Stone Science Future Part 3: Season 4’s Final Chapter Is Set to Change Everything</title>
      <link>https://www.theanimedaily.com/dr-stone-science-future-part-3-season-4-release-date/</link>
      <guid>https://www.theanimedaily.com/dr-stone-science-future-part-3-season-4-release-date/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:45:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>
        &lt;p&gt;Dr. Stone&amp;#160;has never been a typical shōnen anime. From the moment humanity was turned to stone, the series chose science over brute force and logic over luck. Now, with&amp;#160;Dr Stone Science Future Part 3&amp;#160;officially on the horizon, the anime is preparing to close its story with its most ambitious chapter yet. Season 4, titled&amp;#160;Science Future, [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theanimedaily.com/dr-stone-science-future-part-3-season-4-release-date/&quot;&gt;Dr Stone Science Future Part 3: Season 4’s Final Chapter Is Set to Change Everything&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theanimedaily.com&quot;&gt;The Anime Daily&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Happy Marriage Season 3: Is It Happening? Release Date, Story Expectations &amp; Everything We Know So Far</title>
      <link>https://www.theanimedaily.com/my-happy-marriage-season-3/</link>
      <guid>https://www.theanimedaily.com/my-happy-marriage-season-3/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:45:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>
        &lt;p&gt;My Happy Marriage&amp;#160;became one of the most emotionally resonant romance-fantasy anime in recent years. With two beautifully crafted seasons and a special episode announcement already stirring excitement, fans are now asking one big question:&amp;#160;Is My Happy Marriage Season 3 coming, or is the story nearing its end? Let’s break down everything we know so far [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theanimedaily.com/my-happy-marriage-season-3/&quot;&gt;My Happy Marriage Season 3: Is It Happening? Release Date, Story Expectations &amp;#038; Everything We Know So Far&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theanimedaily.com&quot;&gt;The Anime Daily&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honey Lemon Soda Season 2: Release Date Status, Story Expectations, and What Comes Next</title>
      <link>https://www.theanimedaily.com/honey-lemon-soda-season-2-release-date-updates/</link>
      <guid>https://www.theanimedaily.com/honey-lemon-soda-season-2-release-date-updates/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:45:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>
        &lt;p&gt;Honey Lemon Soda&amp;#160;arrived quietly but left a lasting impression. Instead of exaggerated drama, the anime leaned into emotional realism, self-growth, and gentle romance. After the conclusion of the first season, viewers are now asking the same question everywhere:&amp;#160;Will Honey Lemon Soda have a Season 2? As interest continues to grow, here is a complete and [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theanimedaily.com/honey-lemon-soda-season-2-release-date-updates/&quot;&gt;Honey Lemon Soda Season 2: Release Date Status, Story Expectations, and What Comes Next&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theanimedaily.com&quot;&gt;The Anime Daily&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dan Da Dan Season 3: Release Window, New Teaser Visual, Story Direction, and What Comes Next</title>
      <link>https://www.theanimedaily.com/dan-da-dan-season-3-release-date-teaser-story/</link>
      <guid>https://www.theanimedaily.com/dan-da-dan-season-3-release-date-teaser-story/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:45:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>
        &lt;p&gt;Dan Da Dan&amp;#160;has never played it safe. The anime built its reputation on chaos, emotion, and genre defiance, blending supernatural horror with offbeat comedy and unexpected heart. After the intensity of Season 2, fans are now looking ahead to what lies next. With&amp;#160;Dan Da Dan Season 3&amp;#160;officially confirmed, the series is preparing to enter a [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theanimedaily.com/dan-da-dan-season-3-release-date-teaser-story/&quot;&gt;Dan Da Dan Season 3: Release Window, New Teaser Visual, Story Direction, and What Comes Next&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theanimedaily.com&quot;&gt;The Anime Daily&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solo Leveling Season 3: Release Date Update, Story Predictions &amp; Latest Exciting Teases</title>
      <link>https://www.theanimedaily.com/solo-leveling-season-3-release-date-update/</link>
      <guid>https://www.theanimedaily.com/solo-leveling-season-3-release-date-update/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:45:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>
        &lt;p&gt;Solo Leveling&amp;#160;has become one of the biggest anime phenomena of the decade. From its explosive debut to a record-breaking second season, the show redefined adaptation hype and made Sung Jin-woo a household name among anime fans worldwide. The action, emotion, and sheer scale of the story have kept viewers invested — and now the biggest [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theanimedaily.com/solo-leveling-season-3-release-date-update/&quot;&gt;Solo Leveling Season 3: Release Date Update, Story Predictions &amp;#038; Latest Exciting Teases&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theanimedaily.com&quot;&gt;The Anime Daily&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zenshu Season 2: Is It Coming? Release Date, Story Hints, Cast &amp; Everything Known So Far</title>
      <link>https://www.theanimedaily.com/zenshu-season-2-is-it-happening/</link>
      <guid>https://www.theanimedaily.com/zenshu-season-2-is-it-happening/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:45:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>
        &lt;p&gt;Ever since the emotionally layered finale of&amp;#160;Zenshu&amp;#160;Season 1, fans have been asking the same question:&amp;#160;Is Zenshu Season 2 happening or not?&amp;#160;While the creators have remained quiet, growing curiosity around the anime’s future has kept discussions alive. Here’s a complete breakdown of everything known so far about&amp;#160;Zenshu Season 2, including a Season 1 recap, release date [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theanimedaily.com/zenshu-season-2-is-it-happening/&quot;&gt;Zenshu Season 2: Is It Coming? Release Date, Story Hints, Cast &amp;#038; Everything Known So Far&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theanimedaily.com&quot;&gt;The Anime Daily&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue Exorcist Season 6: Release Date Status, Announcement Updates, and What Comes Next</title>
      <link>https://www.theanimedaily.com/blue-exorcist-season-6-release-date-update/</link>
      <guid>https://www.theanimedaily.com/blue-exorcist-season-6-release-date-update/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:45:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>
        &lt;p&gt;Blue Exorcist&amp;#160;has never followed a smooth release path. The anime’s history has been shaped by long gaps, restructured story arcs, and careful returns rather than annual seasons. After the conclusion of&amp;#160;The Blue Night Saga, fans are once again asking a familiar question:&amp;#160;Is Blue Exorcist Season 6 confirmed, and when will it release? Here is a [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theanimedaily.com/blue-exorcist-season-6-release-date-update/&quot;&gt;Blue Exorcist Season 6: Release Date Status, Announcement Updates, and What Comes Next&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theanimedaily.com&quot;&gt;The Anime Daily&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medalist Season 2 Brings Inori Face-to-Face With Higher Expectations</title>
      <link>https://www.theanimedaily.com/medalist-season-2-release-date-update/</link>
      <guid>https://www.theanimedaily.com/medalist-season-2-release-date-update/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:45:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>
        &lt;p&gt;Medalist&amp;#160;emerged as a sports anime that emphasized process over results. The first season focused on beginnings, training, and emotional groundwork rather than competition outcomes. With the story now moving forward, attention has shifted to how that foundation will be tested as the narrative progresses into a more demanding phase. Following the conclusion of Season 1, [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theanimedaily.com/medalist-season-2-release-date-update/&quot;&gt;Medalist Season 2 Brings Inori Face-to-Face With Higher Expectations&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theanimedaily.com&quot;&gt;The Anime Daily&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Re:Zero Season 4 Marks a Turning Point in Subaru’s Journey That Changes Everything</title>
      <link>https://www.theanimedaily.com/re-zero-starting-life-in-another-world-season-4-release-date/</link>
      <guid>https://www.theanimedaily.com/re-zero-starting-life-in-another-world-season-4-release-date/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:45:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded>
        &lt;p&gt;Re:Zero – Starting Life in Another World&amp;#160;has never aimed to be comfortable. Fans connect with it because the anime embraces emotional collapse, harsh consequences, and impossible decisions. Each season pushes Subaru further. After the last arc ended, attention shifted toward what comes next. Season 4 now stands as the series’ most anticipated chapter yet. Re:Zero [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theanimedaily.com/re-zero-starting-life-in-another-world-season-4-release-date/&quot;&gt;Re:Zero Season 4 Marks a Turning Point in Subaru’s Journey That Changes Everything&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theanimedaily.com&quot;&gt;The Anime Daily&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>